Male, 24

Yuri Stepanov



yuri.burkhardt@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/kendzi

Summary

I'm a frontend developer with 3+ years of experience. I have most experience with Angular and React based apps, but I can also assist backend a bit, especially on Node.js + Express.

It is really important for me to actively communicate with my team, making decisions that allow building a beautiful product. My passion is to make things actually work.

Experience

Frontend Developer

Natlex Ltd.

Jun 2019 - Present (2 years 11 months +)

I worked on reducing compile time by splitting existing codebase into separate modules. I also reduced code review time by helping to create a corporate code style and integrating the linter. Improved logging process on frontend, which helped to catch new bugs.

Technologies: Angular, AngularJs, Typescript, SASS, LESS, RxJs, NgRx + Java Spring Boot.

Trainee Frontend Developer

Trinity Digital

Jan 2019 - Mar 2019 (3 months)

Creating hotel booking system. Working closely with latest Angular and Ruby on Rails versions. Performed scientific research, which lead to better performance.

Technologies: Angular, Ruby on Rails.

Education



Petrozavodsk State University (PetrSU)

Bachelor's degree, Information systems and technologies 2015 - 2019

Skills

Angular • React HTML • CSS • SCSS • LESS Javascript • Typescipt • RxJs • NgRx • Redux Express.js